If there's one thing I want you to take away from this module,
このモジュールで覚えておいて欲しいのは
it is that the magic of machine learning comes with quantity, not complexity.
機械学習で重要なのは 複雑さではなく量だということです
Many small machine learning models,
どれも単純で小さい機械学習モデルが
each of which are simple.
多数あるとします
So think of a map's example.
地図の例を考えてみましょう
So if you're building many machine learning models,
現在 多くの機械学習モデルを構築していて
and planning for many more that you may never build,
今後は構築しない可能性がある場合
you want to have an environment where you fail fast.
早めに失敗できる環境が必要です
The idea is that if you're failing fast,
早く失敗すれば
you get the ability to iterate.
やり直すことができるからです
This ability to experiment is critical in the realm of machine learning.
実験できる環境は機械学習において不可欠です
So you want to fail fast and iterate so that you can try a lot of new ideas,
早めに失敗してやり直せば 新しいアイデアも多く試すことができ
and that way, get a lot more successes.
成功例も増えるでしょう
Now when I say a data,
データと言うとき
most people immediately think structured data,
多くの人は構造化データを思い浮かべます
as in data in a database.
データベースのデータのようなものです
But 90 percent of enterprise data is unstructured.
しかし企業データの90%は 非構造化データです
Think emails, video footage, texts, reports,
メール、動画、文字、レポート
catalogs, fashion shoots, events,
カタログ、ファッション撮影、イベント
news, you name it.
ニュースなど
All unstructured data.
これらすべては非構造化データです
Dealing with unstructured data has gotten
非構造化データの処理は容易になりました
a lot easier because of the pre-trained models that we talked about.
すでに触れた訓練済みモデルのおかげです
So think of it an ML pipeline as a way to deal with unstructured data.
MLパイプラインを 非構造化データの処理方法と考えましょう
Take unstructured data, pass them through ML APIs,
非構造化データをML APIで処理すると
and then you are left with entities,
結果は実体、場所、ラベル、人物など
So you don't have to start with unstructured data,
非構造化データで始める必要はなく
process the unstructured data through an ML API and take
非構造化データをML APIで処理して
the results of the ML API as the input to your custom ML model.
その結果を カスタムMLモデルに入力できるのです